It's that time of season
到了那个季节
Alright
好的
I hate this
我讨厌这个
What is it I will call to Bell pepper my girlfriend gifts from Australia
我要从澳大利亚给我的女朋友礼物甜椒叫什么
Capsicums
辣椒
That's fine
没关系
Go for it
去吧
I have never
我从来没有
What are the
什么是
Perfect
完美
Can I sing
我可以唱歌吗
The smell in hoover
胡佛的气味
So what do I do after a D&C
那么在D＆C之后我该怎么办
I don't want to be
我不想成为
Someone taught me how to do this
有人教我怎么做
You and I
你和我
Remember
记得
So what you do this take this out
所以你要怎么做
Like a pumpkin cut in half
像切成两半的南瓜
Alexa and Karen ages
Alexa和Karen年龄
And then there's inside Park you can do
然后在公园里面，你可以做
Call
呼叫
What all do is I cut out the kiss
所有的事情就是我割掉了吻
Dangerous jet Lee
危险，jet Lee
I know there's like a fancy way to do it
我知道有一种很不错的方法
This app
这个程序
Play most recent
最近播放
How many kg are left hand
左手多少公斤
Turn off light
关闭开关
Slices app
切片部位
We are sliced
我们被切成薄片
The work of art
艺术品
So just like any other vegetable find yourself or flat sides for your vegetables not rolling around when you cry
因此，就像其他任何蔬菜一样，您自己或蔬菜的平坦侧面在哭泣时不会滚动
Miniature in the bottom your
底部的微型
Basically you have natural seem so you can see this sort of has a square shape and I'm gonna follow those natural scenes
基本上您看起来很自然，所以您可以看到这种正方形的形状，而我将遵循这些自然场景
As my divided
正如我的分歧
Work my way down the pepper
顺着辣椒往下走
King of the court
宫廷之王
Inside the pepper you'll have some white this is the path we want to remove it going to come in with my parents
胡椒粉里面会有一些白色，这是我们要去除的路径，这将是我父母带进来的
And
Turn that radio
打开收音机
Just like that making a horizontal
就像制作水平
Once I have that removed
一旦我删除了
Then I'm single
那我单身
Come through you'll find it much easier to slice of pepper with the skin side down
来吧，您会发现将皮肤朝下的胡椒切片更容易
If I put the skin up
如果我把皮肤
The night has a tendency to countdown soften the skin because of the flash underneath is much softer than that
夜晚有倒数的趋势，因为下面的闪光灯要柔软得多，因此皮肤柔软
Skin side down
皮肤朝下
Heard
听说